Finding Aid for the Cecil Sims
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Sims, Cecil Papers
1914-1967
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0393
16.80 linear_feet
Biographical Sketch
June 20, 1893 Born in Atlanta, Georgia. Parents - Charles M. and Moselle Park Sims.
Early education in Birmingham, Alabama.
1911 Graduated Vanderbilt University.
1914 Graduated Vanderbilt Law School, and received the Founders Medal for outstanding scholastic achievement.
1917-1919 Served in U.S. Army, in the 322nd Infantry, 8lst Division.
1921 Married Grace Wilson.
1925 Served in Tennessee State Senate.
1938-1942 National President of Vanderbilt University Alumni Association.
1945-1947 Member and secretary of the Committee on Revision of the Tennessee Constitution.
1948 Delegate to the Democratic National Convention.
1948 Drafted a compact for regional education which was approved and signed at a meeting of the governers of the southern states held in Tallahassee, Florida, Feb. 7, 1948.
1953 Delegate to the Tennessee Limited Constitutional Convention.
June 22, 1968 Died, Nashville, Tennessee.
Member: Board of Trust, Executive Committee, and Athletic Committee of Vanderbilt University. Was a director of National Life and Accident Insurance Co., Spur Distributing Co. Inc., Hermitage Portland Cement Co., Air Utilities Inc., Board of Education of Davidson County, Tenn., Board of United Cerebral Palsy of Middle Tenn. an chairman of the 1st Cerebral Palsy Telethon,l965.
- Correspondence - Outgoing. June 14, 1914 August 10, 1967. (Box 1-5)
- Outgoing correspondence of 3,113 letters. Chronologically arranged by days and months, letters are holographic, typescript, and carbon copies. Thirteen undated letters found at end of outgoing correspondence.
- Correspondence - Incoming. Incoming correspondence of 2,451 letters, alphabetically arranged. Letters signed with one name only, letters with illegible signatures, and letters without signatures are found at end of incoming correspondence. Letters mostly typescript, holographic, and carbon copies. (Box 5-11)
- Research And Lecture Notes. There are approximately 1000 pages of holographic and typescript notes. The notes cover a variety of subjects, including legal transactions, bees, the legal profession, and will writing. There are several rough drafts of speeches included. There are also several notebooks kept by Cecil Sims while he was a soldier (W.W.l). (Box 12, Box 13)
- Writings By Sims. Material includes 11 essays and research papers dealing with miscellaneous subjects. Papers are alphabetically arranged by title: Agricultural Obstetrics, or Birth on the Farm; The Doctrine of Assumption of Risk; Labor Disputes; Language And The Law (book review); A Pattern For The Future; Shall We Fight In The Lowlands, Or Retreat To The Mountains?; Social Security; Teaching Ethics In The Broader Sense; Who Will Survive, Homo Sapiens Or The Insects?; 2 untitled works found at end. Writings are holographic, typescript, and carbon copies. (Box 13)
- Business Papers. Material consists of’ approximately 300 items, including bills, receipts, bank deposit slips, and cancelled checks. (Box 14)
- Newspapers And Newspaper Clippings. There are 16 newspapers, mostly copies of “The Anniston Star” and “The Birmingham News”, and approximately 200 newspaper clippings. Material dates from 1917 to 1968. Newspapers will be found first, followed by clippings by and about Cecil Sims, and clippings which are neither by nor about Sims. (Box 14-15)
- Magazines And Magazine Clippings. Material includes 10 magazines, alphabetically arranged: the ina world: labor case Digest the Madison Survey; the Open Road for Boys; Southern Telephone News; Tennessee Market Bulletin; The University Of Michigan Law Quadrangle Notes; Vanderbilt Alumnus (6 issues); Vanderbilt Law Alumni Newsletter; Viewpoint On Taxes And Estate Planning. Also included are approximately 100 magazine clippings which cover a variety of subjects, from politics to lawyers to bees. (Box 15-16)
- Speeches And Statements. Material consists of speeches, addresses, and statements issued by Sims and others. Those by Sims are found first, alphabetically arranged by title: Commencement Address at Webb School June 2, 1948; Shall We Fight In The Lowlands Or Retreat To The Mountains? Who Will Survive, Homo Sapiens, Or The Insects?. Untitled speeches and statements follow. (Box 16)
- Speeches and statements not by Sims: Address Delivered By Hammond Fowler, Railroad And Public Utilities Commissioner Of The State Of Tennessee, At Harriman, Tennessee On October 25, 1949, By Transcription, From Station WHBT, Under Sponsorship Of The Harriman Teachers Association; Campaign Opening Address by Mayor P.R. Olgiati; The Centenary Of Associate Justice John Catron of The United States Supreme Court, Address of Walter Chandler; The Erskine Tradition And The Free Society, by Lucius E. Burch, Jr.; The Hard Way Is The Only Way, by Pierre S. duPont; The Judiciary Bill Should Not Pass, by Joseph c. O’Mahoney; Lawyers, Judges, And Law Schools, remarks of Sam L. Felts; Madison Avenue? Or the Street Where You Live?, by J. Edward Dean; Synthetic Rubber, b Fulton Lewis, jr.; Statement Of The Chamber Of Commerce Of The United States On H.R. 3000, The National Education Improvement Act Of 1963 Submitted To The House Committee On Education And Labor March 8, 1963; 2 statements made by Vanderbilt University concerning the admission of Negro students.
- Photographs. Material consists of approximately 50 photographs, mostly of Cecil Sims, dating from his early life to his later life. Other photographs are of miscellaneous people, places, things. There are 5 oversized photographs which will be kept in Manuscripts Tray 13. (Box 16)
- Certificates And Awards. There are 31 certificates and awards which had been given to Cecil Sims. Seven of these are oversized and will be found in Manuscripts Tray 13. (Box 17)
- Regional Education. The material consists mainly of typescript and printed resolutions, contracts, memorandums, minutes, reports, agendas, programs, pamphlets and miscellaneous publications, newspaper and magazine clippings, relating to regional education. Also included are approximately 50 pages of holographic notes on the subject taken by Cecil Sims. (Box 17-19)
- Return Of Alien Property. There are approximately 200 items relating to the return of alien property after World War II. The material includes notes and writings on the subject by Cecil Sims, miscellaneous reports, translations of German articles, newspaper and magazine clippings, and various publications. (Box 19)
- Segregation. There are approximately 150 items, mostly holographic notes and typescript writings by Sims; pamphlets and reprints; miscellaneous writings and blurbs by others; and newspaper and magazine clippings relating to segregation. (Box 20)
- Constitutional Revision. Material includes approximately 30 newspaper clippings, and 7 publications, alphabetically arranged by title, relating to constitutional revision: The Apportionment Of Legislative Seats; The Fifth Annual Report Tennessee Taxpayers Association For The Year 1936; Journal and Proceedings Constitutional Convention State Of Tennessee 1953; Methods Of Constitutional Revision; Model State Constitution; Papers On Constitutional Revision; Report Of Constitution Revision Commission. Also included is a copy of the constitutional amendments adopted by the constitutional convention for ratification by the people of Tennessee, November 3, 1953. (Box 20-21)
- Democratic National Convention, 1948. There are approximately 75 items relating to the convention. Included are: newspaper clippings; pamphlets; a copy of the proposed Democratic platform; and miscellaneous notes and flyers. (Box 22)
- Writings By Others. Material includes papers; poems and essays, typescript and carbon copies, alphabetically arranged by title: Arguments In Appellate Courts, by William Renwick Riddell; How Long?, by Grace Armstrong Allen; Immortalizing Gall, by Alec B. Stevenson; Loyalty, by Elbert Hubbard; One Full Life, by S.W. McGill; Portrait In Black And Gold, by Jan Rouch; “We Must All Hang Together Or We Shall All Hang Separately”, by J.M. Gardenhire. (Box 22)
- Miscellaneous Writings. There are about 300 pages, mostly typescript and carbon copies, which include titled works that are unsigned; memorandums; untitled and unsigned works; by-laws; minutes of meetings; miscellaneous loose sheets. Titled works are alphabetically arranged: The Constitution Of The United States; Constitutional Government In General; Kennedy, Castro And Communism; The Legal Position of the Common Stock Holder; A Proposal For Hospital Service In Nashville And Davidson County; Untitled booklet which is dedicated “to the Inventors of Maneuvers and Army Paperwork”. (Box 22)
- Resolutions. There are 11 memorial resolutions, alphabetically arranged by the name of the deceased: Francis Marion Bass, Jr.; Frank A. Berry; Richard Newell Coolidge; Cornelius Abernathy Craig; William I. Edwards, Jr.; John Mason Houghland; Orrin Henry Ingram; Littell Rust: Charles Henry Rutherford, Sr.: Charles Milton Sims: Mozelle Rebecca Park Sims. There are 3 other resolutions, 2 relating to Vanderbilt University, and 1 relating to the appointment of an additional u.s. District Judge for the Middle and Eastern Districts of the State of Tennessee. (Box 23)
- Biographical Resumes. Material includes approximately 20 biographical sketches of Sims and others. (Box 23)
- Reports. There are 6 reports, mostly typescript and carbon copies, alphabetically arranged by title: Prospectus St. Louis- Southern Airlines Inc.: Report of Committee on Legal Education and Admission to the Bar; Report of committee on Methods of Making Nominations for Election to Board Membership, Board of Trust of Vanderbilt University, May 4, 1956: Report of James L. McDevitt, National Director, Committee On Political Education, AFL-CIO, To Administrative Committee, AFLCIO Committee On Political Education, August 1962: The Webb School Development Program, by Charles s. Ragland: Report of the Standing Committee On Jurisprudence And Law Reform. (Box 23)
- Legal Papers. Approximately 200 typescript and carbon copy pages of contracts, deeds, resumes of court transactions, legal opinions, oaths, and summaries of various court cases. (Box 23)
- Government Publications. Included are congressional bills, reports, resolutions, and publications (Congressional Record). Material refers mainly to u.s. Congress, but a few items do refer to Tennessee State Congress. (Box 23)
- Reprints. Four, alphabetically arranged by title: The Colleagues Of Mr. Chips, by Samuel Sandmel; The Confederate. Constitution Today, by H.C. and John T. Nixon; The Dragonflies Of The Reelfoot Lake Area, by John Koen; Federal Trade Commission And Trademarks, by Mercer L. Stockel!; “Sawney” Webb, by William R. Webb, Jr. (Box 23)
- Pamphlets. Twenty-five, dealing with a variety of subjects, including social security, the Webb School, communism, negroes, life insurance, and trucks. (Box 24)
- Miscellaneous Publications. Twelve, alphabetically arranged by title: AGB Reports; Agenda For The Meeting Of The Board Of Trust May S-6, 1966 And Annual Reports (Vanderbilt University); The Year Book of the Coffee House Club 1931-1932; Excerpts From The Annual Reports Of The Deans 1966-67 For The Board Of Trust (Vanderbilt University); Historical Sketches Blst Division Area; The Living Endowment Of Vanderbilt University A Handbook; The Mirror; Public Schools Of Davidson County, Tennessee; The Story of World Trade; Vanderbilt Calendar; Vanderbilt Gazette; Washington Report (Box 24)
- Programs. There are about 30 programs for various events, such as conventions, conferences, dedications. Many deal with affairs held at Vanderbilt University. (Box 24)
- Miscellaneous. Approximately 100 items, including flyers and blurbs, application forms, lists of names and addresses, and maps of France. Also included is a holographic paragraph signed by O.W. Holmes, dated March 8, 1931. (Box 25)
Index of Incoming Correspondents
This is a name index of the correspondents of Cecil Sims. The figure (or figures) in parentheses immediately following each name denotes the total number of letters from that person in the collection; the dates given are those which are on the letters. The full name of the writer is given whenever possible; 35 letters are signed with one name only, and 9 letters are without any names. The last number given refers to the box in which the correspondence may be found.
ABELES, Victor (4) - Sept. 20, 1939; June 16, 1939; Mar. 21, 1940; May 14, 1940; 5
ABERNATHY, W. K. (1) - May 2, 1935; 5
ADAMS, A. A. (12) - Jan. 3, 1939; Apr. 10, 1939; July 10, 1939; Oct. 10, 1939; Jan. 2, 1940; Apr. 5, 1940; July 30, 1940; Jan. 7, 1941; June 30, 1941; Jan. 5, 1942; July 31, 1942; n.d.; 5
ADAMS, Adam G. (1) - Nov. 6, 1956; 5
ADAMS, Alf (3) -Nov. 21, 1943; June 4, 1944; June 7, 1944; 5
ADAMS, David (1) - n.d.; 5
ADAMS, E. S. (1) -Oct. 30, 1940 (to Joseph W. Byrns, Jr.); 5
ADAMS, E. Gerry (2) - July 15, 1933; July 28, 1933; 5
ADAMS, Floyd H. (1) - Oct. 16, 1935; 5
ADAMS, Lloyd S. (4) -Mar 11, 1952 (to E.M. Morgan); Apr. 24, 1952 (to Charles L. Neely); May 2, 1952; n.d.; 5
ADAMS, Robert P. (1) -May 6, 1943; 5
ADAMS, W. N., Jr. (1) -July 21, 1934; 5
ADAMSON, Evan Lloyd (1) - July 5, 1933; 5
ADERHOLD, 0. C. (1) - May 13, 1961; 5
AGEE, Macon (2) - June 10, 1935; Feb. 10, 1938; 5
ALEXANDER, Ben F. (1) -May 3, 1939 (to Henry B. Witham); 5
ALEXANDER, C. C., Jr. (1) -Sept. 27, 1965; 5
ALEXANDER, Harmon (1) - July 5; 5
ALEXANDER, Henry C. (2) - Dec. 7, 1942; May 16, 1947; 5
ALEXANDER, V. J. (14) -Oct. 18, 1933; Oct. 23, 1933;’ Oct. 26, 1933; Oct 28, 1933; Nov. 27, 1933; Dec. 8, 1933; July 27, 1935; Aug. 29, 1935; May 5,1941; Feb. 14, 1946; Sept. 15, 1959; July 12, 1961; Oct. 11, 1963; May 18, 1964; 5
ALEXANDER, Will W. (3) - Dec. 12, 1936; Dec. 22, 1936; Jan. 11, 1937; 5
ALFS, C. G. (1) - May 5, 1947; 5
ALLEN, Clifford (2) - July 9, 1962; Jan. 31, 1964; 5
ALLEN, G. F., Jr. (1) - July 15, 1948; 5
ALLEN, J. P. (1) - Jan. 17, 1938; 5
ALLEN, Tip H., Jr. (1) -May 30, 1958; 5
ALLEN, W. H. (1) - Dec. 14, 1949; 5
ALLEY, James B. (2) - May 13, 1937; Sept. 24, 1952; 5
AMBROSE, W. L. Jr. (2) -Feb. 13, 1957; Feb. 13, 1957 (to Walter c. Chandler); 5
AMES, Ed -(1) - June 14, 1966; 5
ANDERSON, A. F. (1) - Dec. 11, 1934; 5
ANDERSON, Agatha A. (1) - Dec. 15, 1949; 5
ANDERSON, Anna Marie (1) - Dec. 10; 5
ANDERSON, Hu C. (5) - Feb. 13, 1933; Feb. 24, 1940; Feb. 24, 1940 (to Mrs. M. W. Haggard); Aug. 14, 1941; Mar 8, 1952; 5
ANDERSON, Robert C. (1) - Mar. 9, 1959; 5
ANDERSON, T. J. (1) - Oct. 1, 1936; 5
ANDERSON, W. J. (1) - July 15, 1943; 5
ANDREWS, Forrest (1) - Feb. 3, 1961; 5
APPEN, H. V. (1) - Jan. 30, 1963; 5
ARCHIE, George (1) - Dec. 1, 1964; 5
ARMBRUSTER, Mary E. (1) - Apr. 8, 1949; 5
ARMISTEAD, George H. Jr. (12) - Jan. 23, 1934; Feb. 2, 1934; Jan. 28, 1935; Nov. 6, 1936; June 21, 1937; Sept. 3, 1937; Jan. 11, 1938; Apr. 28, 1938; Mar. 17, 1947; Apr. 28, 1938; Mar. 17, 1947; Apr. 18, 1953; n.d.; 5
ARMISTEAD, Hunter (2) - Aug. 24, 1959; July 28, 1960; 5
ARMISTEAD, Parkes (2) -Oct. 2, 1933 (to V. J. Alexander); Oct. 3, 1933; 5
ARMSTRONG, Irma W. (1) - n.d. (5)
ARMSTRONG, Walter P. (5) -Mar 14, 1933; Aug. 11, 1933; Sept. 5, 1933, May 16, 1934; Apr. 22, 1937; 5
ARMSTRONG, Walter P. Jr. (1) - Jan. 21, 1965; 5
ARMSTRONGS, The Walter (1) - 1966; 5
ARNOLD, E. C. (1) - Mar 24, 1936; 5
ASHCRAFT, Tom (1) -Jan. 16, 1963 (to Dave Morrah); 5
ASHLEY, Barret (2) -Aug. 10, 1962; n.d.; 5
AUSTIN, H. Leroy (1) -Apr. 17, 1964; 5
AYCOCK, Charles B. (1) - Sept. 6, 1960; 5
BAADE, Paul W. (3) - Jan. 9, 1939; Sept. 26, 1942; Oct. 16, 1943; 5
BACHMAN, Nathan L. (6) -July 7, 1933; Aug. 8, 1934; Nov. 14, 1934; Mar. 9, 1935; Mar. 18, 1935; June 29, 1935; 5
BAILEY, Ferriss C. (1) - Mar 12, 1957; 5
BAIN, Chapman (2) -Nov. 7, 1957 (to Samuel Halper); Sept. 17, 1963; 5
BALL, Ed (2) -Apr. 19, 1948; Apr. 6, 1961; 5
BALLS, H. 0. (1) - Apr. 16, 1965; 5
BANKS, L. Frazer (1) - Apr. 11, 1955; 5
BANKS, Paul, Jr. (1) - Dec. 15, 1960; 5
BAPTIST, R. B. (1) -Aug. 7, 1948; 5
BARBA, Horace M. (2) - Mar 23, 1934; May 8, 1934; 5
BARBARIN, A. E. (2) - Aug. 9, 1933; Aug. 11, 1933; 5
BARFIELD, Nell (1) - Oct. 28, 1940; 5
BARHAM, Charles Jr. (1) - Jan. 26, 1937; 5
BARKER, Forrest W. (1) - Sept. 5, 1966; 5
BARKSDALE, J. A. (2) - Jan. 4, 1951; Oct. 17, 1951 (both to John E. Ivey, Jr.); 5
BARKSDALE, John M. (1) - Mar. 11, 1949; 5
BARNES, F. W. (1) - Aug. 1, 1956; 5
BARNETT, Joseph W. (1)- Feb. 21, 1949; 5
BARRETT, R. N. (1) - Jan. 17, 1940; 5
BARRS, Burton (1) - June 7, 1939; 5
BASS, BERRY & SIMS (6) - Feb. 1936; June 24, 1938; Nov. 15, 1938; Dec. 14, 1938; Apr. 3, 1941; Nov. 14, 1955; 5
BASS, F. M. (9) - July 30, 1918; Nov. 12, 1918; Dec. 2, 1918; Oct. 23, 1934; Jan. 9, 1936; Oct. 16, 1936; Jan. 22, 1937; June 25, 1938; n.d.; 5
BASS, Jack M. (1) - Mar. 12, 1937; 5
BASS, James 0. (2) - Sept. 30, 1944; Aug. 23, 1945; 5
BASS, Neil (2Y - May 2, 1934; Apr. 24, 1939; 5
BASS, Ross (3)
Bass, Warner, (1); Oct. 31, 1962; 5
Bassine, Charles C., (13); Sept. 12, 1947, May 12, 1950, Sept. 8, 1950, Feb. 26, 1951, Sept. 11, 1951, Sept. 11, 1951, Oct. 15, 1951, Sept. 2, 1952, Apr. 10, 1959, June 19, 1959, July 11, 1962, (n.d.), (n.d.); 5
Bateman, C.H., (1); June 23, 1946; 5
Bateman, Mrs. H.L., (2); Jan. 5, 1954, Oct. 1, 1959; 5
Bates, Fred, (1); Oct. 15, 1933; 5
Baum, Myron.C., (2); Jan. 11, 1961, Jan. 26, 1961; 6
Baxter, Frank C., (1); Feb. 12, 1962; 6
Bayley, Frank~., (1); Jan. 30, 1957; 6
Baynton, Harold, (1); Jan. 6, 1959; 6
Beaird, Anna Lou, (1); Sept. 2, 1959; 6
Beaird, Edith, (1); Jan. 7, 1936; 6
Beard, J .N., (l); Feb. 9, 1933; 6
Beard, Leslie P., (1); Aug. 29, 1952; 6
Bearden, WalterS., (1); Apr. 28, 1942; 6
Beasley, JohnS. II, (1); Jan. 11, 1954; 6
Beauchamp, William B., (3); Nov. 19, 1932, Feb. 23, 1933, Jan. 16, 1934; 6
Beck, Harry C., (1); June 3, 1939; 6
Beck, Ira A., (1); Aug. 30, 1938; 6
Beckman, F.woods, (1); July 2, 1948; 6
Beehan N.G., (1); Oct. 31, 1957; 6
Beehan, Nicky Jr., (2); Apr. 26, 1961, Aug. 8, 1961; 6
Beekman, Bogu. ,Leake, Stephens, & Black, (1); Jan. 3, 1938; 6
Beeler, Roy H., (2); July 3, 1946, July 8, 1948; 6
Bejach, L.D., (1); Aug. 18, 1948; 6
Benedict, Andrew B. (3); Feb. 12, 1946, July 28, 19~4, (n.d.); 6
Bennett, Anne, (1); Nov. 19, 1959; 6
Benson, Maxwell E., (2); Jan. 22, 1964, Aug. 1, 1964; 6
Bent, Michael J., (2); Dec. 1949, Apr. 7, 1950 (toM. Don Clawson); 6
Bergheim, Melvin L., (1); Sept. 17, 1962; 6
Berry, F.A., (1); May 1, 1937; 6
Berry, Tyler III, (1); Mar. 1, 1960; 6
Berry, William W., (2); Feb. 6, 1944, Aug. 10, 1944; 6
Bess, F.M. Jr., (l); Feb. 12, 1946; 6
Bethel, Billie, (1); Nov. 4, 1965; 6
Bethshares, T.P., (6); June 3, 1933, May 27, 1936, Nov. 10, 1937, July 18, 1938, Apr. 29, 1939, Jan. 15, 1943; 6
Bethurum, Douglas J., (2); June 7, 1933, June 9, 1933; 6
Bethurum, G.R., (1); Sept. 7, 1965; 6
Bickmore, H.L., (l); May 20, 1946; 6
Bidwell, Nathan B., (1); Oct. 30, 1944; 6
Bigger, A.C., (l); Jan. 31, 1935; 6
Biles, Ruby, (1); Jan. 17, 1938; 6
Billings, F. Tremaine Jr., (2); Dec. 19, 1959, Sept. 27, 1965; 6
Binkley, Don, (2); Mar. 20, 1962, July 27, 1962; 6
Bird, R.J., (1); Mar. 21, 1936; 6
Bisalski, Edwin M., (1); (n.d.); 6
Black, Eugene R., (l); June 12, 1952; 6
Blackburn, George, (1); July 31, 1962; 6
Blackman, Harry J., (2); Mar. 16, 1964 (to John M. Fowler), Oct. 28, 1964 (to Bradford H. Rice); 6
Blair, Harrison D., (2); Dec. 16, 1938, Dec. 17, 1938; 6
Blake, R.E., (1); Mar. 26, 1945; 6
Bloch, Charles J., (1); Oct. 14, 1948 (to Jim McCord); 6
Bomar, Lynn, (1); Feb. 23, 1940; 6
Bomar, Wrenne, (1); (n.d.); 6
Bosecker, Carl E., (1); Apr. l, 1965; 6
Bottiggi, Lou, (1); Feb. 6, 1967; 6
Boult, Reber, (3); July 16, 1948, Nov. 9, 1962, Nov. 24, 1965; 6
Bowe, S.J., (1); Dec. 10, 1946; 6
Bowen, Bill, (1); (n.d.); 6
Bowling, W. Kerby, (1); Aug. 7, 1963; 6
Bowman, O.B., (1); Jan. 18, 1955; 6
Boyd, Henry W. Jr., (1); May 27, 1941; 6
Bozeman, Frank C., (1); Apr. 8, 1955; 6
Bracy, Gladys, (1); Sept. 6, 1966; 6
Bradbury, Jack, (1); May 17, 1961; 6
Bradford, J.C., (1); Feb. 5, 1944; 6
Bradford, Mark, (1); Aug. 19, 1935; 6
Branam, Darwin, (1); July 19, 1967 (to Grace W. Sima); 6
Brandon, Anna M. Tishel, (1); July 27, 1959; 6
Brandon, Frank C., (3); Jan. 27, 1946, Feb. 8, 1946, apr. 22, 1959; 6
Brandon, Morris, {1); Jan. 13, 1938 (to Charles N. tiurch); 6
Brandon, Newman, (1); May 1, 1959; 6
Branscomb, Harvie, (8); Oct. 8, 1947, Nov. 18, 1947, July 19, 1948, Sept. 26, 1949, Feb. 6, 1959, June 3, 1959, Aug. 21, 1959, Aug. 21, 1959; 6
Bratton, Frank N., (1); Dec. 9, 1966; 6
Brennan, J.G., (1); Oct. 13, 1937 (to Judge Fletcher); 6
Britt, A.S., (1); July 24, 1961, 6
Broadbent, A.B., (2); Jan. 14, 1941, Jan. 8, 1946; 6
Brooks, A.L., (1); Feb. 13, 1933; 6
Brooks, Hayden, (1); Nov. 5, 1941; 6
Broome, Harvey, (1); Jan. 30, 1957; 6
Brown, Enoch, (1); June 1, 1954; 6
Brown, Harris, (1); Aug. 29, 1958; 6
Brown, Herbert E., (2); Sept 27, 1938, Oct. 3, 1938; 6
Brown, J.N., (1); June 22, 1938; 6
Hrown, Murray C., (2); Dec. 19, 1949, (n.d.); 6
Hrown, Vernon H., {1); Aug. 4, 1956; 6
Brown, Warren C., (1); (n.d.); 6
Browning, Gordon, (7); May 4, 1949 (to William H. Wicker), Kay 5, 1949, July 11, 1949 Oct. 13, 1950, Oct. 24, 1950, July 27, 1951, Sept. 12, 1952; 6
Bruegge, John Vorder, (2); July 23, 1935, Apr. 24, 1945; 6
Bryan, E.E., (1); Apr. 8, 1963 (to Edwin S. Gardner); 6
Bryan, Ross H., (2); Feb. 2,1962, Feb. 12, 1962 (to Earl E. Baldwin); 6
Bryant, Carl, (1); Mar. 26, 1934; 6
Bryant, Earl, (18); Feb.10, 1933, Nov. 21, 1933, Nov. 29, 1933, Jan. 4, 1934, Jan. 20, 1934, Feb. 26, 1934, Mar. 1, 1934, Mar. 14, 1934, Apr. 3, 1934, Apr. 23, 1934, Apr. 28, 1934, May 29, 1934, June 13, 1934, Jan. 3, 1935, Feb. 12, 1935, Mar. 30, 1935, Apr. 2, 1935, Sept. 7, 1935; 6
Bryant, Pat, (1); June 4, 1936; 6
Buck, Emily B., (3); July 27, 1951, Jan. 17, 1952, Feb. 9, 1952; 6
Bucklin, WalterS., (1); Aug. 6, 1940 (to Frank A. Berry); 6
Buford, James L., (1); Dec. 24, 1957; 6
Bugg, Hazel C., (1); (n.d.); 6
Bugg, Mayme, (1); Dec. 30, 1949; 6
bullard, M.M., (1); July 18, 1963; 6
Bunton, W.D., (1); Nov. 17, 1959; 6
Burch, Charles N., (1); Nov. 26, 1937; 6
Burch, Lucius E. Jr., (2); Feb. 6, 1957, Sept. 12, 1958; 6
Burney, Cecil E., (1); June 19, 1962; 6
Burnham, W.H., (2); Sept. 16, 1939 (to R.A. Shillinglaw), Sept. 18, 1939 (to R.A. Shillinglaw); 6
Burns, Howard F., (2); Oct. 25, 1949, June 2, 1959; 6
Burns, Howard H., (1); May 8, 1956; 6
Burna, Jim, (1); Mar. 23, 1949; 6
Burrow, Wm. F., (6); June 6, 1934, July 31, 1943, Aug. 16, 1943, Jan. 25, 1957, Sept. 14, 1961, Aug. 8, 1962; 6
Burton, Joe W., (1); Mar. 10, 1947; 6
Burton, Percy, (1); Aug. 14, 1937; 6
Burton, William F. Jr., (1); (n.d.); 6
Bussey, James R., (2); Jan. 2, 1934, Sept. 13, 1934; 6
Butler, Bailey c., (1); May 18, 1933; 6
Byrd, Benjamin F., (1); Nov. 15, 1949; 6
Byrd, Dan, (1); Apr.26, 1960; 6
Byrd, Harry F., (1); July 1, 1948 (to Adolph Skinner); 6
Byrns, Joseph W. Jr., (34); Mar. 14, 1934, Dec. 23, 1934~ (to Cedric Hunt), Dec. 24, 1934, June 14, 1935, June 27, 1935, May 12, 1936, Feb. 21, 1939, Kay 11, 1939, May 11, 1939 (to Connelly Edwards), July 20, 1939, Nov. 3, 1939, Feb. 5, 1940, Feb. 20, 1940, Feb. 28, 1940, Mar. 4, 1940, Mar. 9, 1940, Mar. 22, 1940, Apr. 4, 1940, May 15, 194o, May 23, 1940, May 25, 1940, May 25, 1940, June 7, 1940, June 7, 1940, June 13, 194o, July 5, 1940, July 26, 1940, Aug. 12, 1940., Aug. 21, 1940, Sept. 16, 1940, Oct. 11, 1940, Nov. 14, 1940, Nov. 15, 1940 (to J. Percy Priest), Nov. 26, 1945; 6
Cabot, Charles Raymond, (2); Nov. 23, 1938, (n.d.); 6
Calbert, Jack Len, (3); Mar. 22, 1957, Apr. 12, 1957, Sept. 11, 1957; 6
Caldwell, Frances, (1); Apr. 10, 1947; 6
Caldwell, Millard,F., (5); Oct. 6, 1949, Nov. 7, 1950, Nov. 17, 1950, Jan. 4, 1951, June 26, 1962; 6
Callis, Pete, (1); Apr. 19, 1937; 6
Camp, Harry W., (1); Jan. 18, 1962; 6
Camp, Scott, (1); Apr. 28, 1961; 6